DES Action USA records, 1939-2016 (bulk 1975-2014)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS AND AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS
  - Videotapes [Access copies needed]
    - POV on DES A Healthy Baby Girl (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Helfand A Healthy Baby Girl (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Judith Helfand Productions: A Healthy Baby Girl (non-broadcast version) (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - The bitter taste of a miracle drug; Stéphane Mercurio, Catherine Sinet, France, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Marsha Vanderford CNN - Interview CDC-DES (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - KOLO-TV DES Story, 11 Mar 2003 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - KOLO-TV Reno DES Daughter Kim Mazares, 2003 March 20 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - DES Dr Janet Pregler Chapters 9 and 2, 2003 May (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - DES Dr Janet Pregler Chapter 7, 2003 May 28 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- SERIES IX. OVERSIZE
  - Artifact
    - "Ask Your Mother" campaign keychains, circa 1983 (Box 21)
    - "Bad Karma for Big Pharma" t-shirt, 2007 (Box 24)
  - News article, 2003 (Map-case Flat File drawer 68)
  - Posters, 1979-1994, undated (Map-case Flat File drawer 68)